{
    "posts": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "json-server",
        "author": "typicode"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "answer": [
          {
            "question": "who has fastest knockout in UFC history",
            "answer": "Nate"
          },
          {
            "question": "Who has score the 100 international Centuries",
            "answer": "Sachin"
          },
          {
            "question": "Top crypto currency",
            "answer": "Bitcoin"
          },
          {
            "question": "which Team has won 5 Titles in IPL",
            "answer": "CSK"
          },
          {
            "question": "PKL 9th Season winner",
            "answer": "JP"
          },
          {
            "question": "which player has Highest Runs in IPL",
            "answer": "Virat"
          },
          {
            "question": "2023 IPL winners",
            "answer": "RCB"
          },
          {
            "question": "who is Richest UFC fighter in the History",
            "answer": "Usman"
          },
          {
            "question": "which crypto has 20million$ Marketcap",
            "answer": "XRP"
          },
          {
            "question": "which INDIAN Captain won the ICC Trophies in All Formates.",
            "answer": "Ms Dhoni"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "comments": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "body": "some comment",
        "postId": 1
      }
    ],
    "profile": {
      "name": "typicode"
    }
  }